<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info_backup_title">バックアップ &amp; 復元</string>
    <string name="info_backup_content"><![CDATA[<h2>ローカルバックアップ</h2><p><b>ファイルへのバックアップ</b>は、データベース全体をZIPファイルとして任意の場所に保存できます。</p><p><b>自動バックアップ</b>は、データが変更されるたびに選択したフォルダへ自動的に保存します。</p><p><b>ファイルから復元</b>は、以前にエクスポートしたZIPをインポートします。現在のすべてのデータが置き換えられます。</p><h2>クラウドバックアップ</h2><p>クラウドバックアップは、暗号化されたコピーをGoogleドライブに保存します。パスフレーズがあるのはご本人だけです。</p><p><b>自動バックアップ</b>は、変更のたびに自動的にアップロードします。</p><p><b>今すぐバックアップ</b>は、自動バックアップの設定に関係なく、即座にアップロードを開始します。</p><p><b>パスフレーズ</b>はバックアップを暗号化します。デバイスには保存されません。パスフレーズがないと、クラウドバックアップを復元できません。</p><p>最大5つのバックアップバージョンが保持され、古いものは自動的に削除されます。</p><h2>デバイス間の同期</h2><p>Googleドライブに接続すると、<b>デバイス間の同期</b>を有効にして、同じバックアップにサインインしているすべてのデバイス間でデータを継続的に同期できます。</p><p>一つのデバイスで行った変更は他のデバイスに反映され、同期リストからデバイスの名前変更や削除ができます。</p><h2>復元</h2><p>バックアップを復元すると<b>現在のすべてのデータが置き換えられます</b>。復元が成功するとアプリが再起動します。</p><p>クラウド復元には、バックアップ作成時に使用したパスフレーズが必要です。</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_banksync_title">銀行同期</string>
    <string name="info_banksync_content"><![CDATA[<h2>How it works</h2><p>MoneyM imports your bank transactions as <b>suggestions</b> — nothing is added to your books until you accept it. Rejected suggestions are never asked about again, but stay visible under Rejected.</p><h2>Set up Enable Banking</h2><p>Bank access runs through <b>Enable Banking</b>, which provides PSD2/open-banking coverage for supported European banks and countries.</p><ul><li>Create an account at <a href="https://enablebanking.com">enablebanking.com</a> and open the Control Panel.</li><li>Register an application in the <b>production</b> environment (sandbox cannot reach real banks) and set its redirect URL to exactly <a href="https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html">https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html</a>.</li><li>Download the application's private key (PEM file). It is shown only once — keep it safe.</li><li>Copy the Application ID shown on the application page.</li><li>Activate the application by <b>linking a supported bank account</b>: choose the country, your bank and the account type (personal or business), then sign in at your bank to confirm. Availability depends on the bank and country you pick.</li></ul><h2>Connect in the app</h2><p>Paste the Application ID and the key contents into the Bank sync screen and tap <b>Save and validate</b>. Then tap <b>Connect a bank</b>: choose the same country and bank and approve access in the browser. You are sent back to the app automatically; if not, paste the redirect link manually.</p><p>Assign each linked bank account to a wallet so accepted transactions land in the right place.</p><h2>Good to know</h2><p>Bank consent is valid for up to <b>180 days</b>; reconnect when the app asks.</p><p>Automatic sync runs when the app starts, at most every 6 hours. <b>Sync now</b> works anytime.</p><p>Only booked transactions are imported — recent card payments can show up a day or two later, once your bank books them.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_title">AI分析</string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_content"><![CDATA[<h2>スナップショットとツール</h2><p><b>スナップショット</b>は、選択した年のコンパクトな概要（その期間の合計・カテゴリ・残高）をモデルに送信します。高速で、すべてのエンジンで動作し、その年に関する質問に最適です。</p><p><b>ツール</b>は、モデルが全履歴を検索し、必要なレコードだけを取得できるようにします。複数年にまたがる自由な質問に最適です。一部の小さなモデルはツールに対応していません。その場合、アプリは自動的にスナップショットに切り替わります。</p><h2>デバイス上での処理</h2><p>すべての分析は<b>完全にデバイス上</b>で実行されます。あなたの財務データや質問が端末から出ることはなく、いかなるサーバーにも送信されません。</p><p>代償は品質です。デバイス上のモデルはクラウドのモデルよりはるかに小さいため、誤りが多く、細部を見落とし、推論の信頼性も低くなります。<b>小さいモデルほど性能が劣ります</b>。極小モデルは高速ですが非力で、より大きなデバイスモデルは低速ですが高性能です。最良のデバイスモデルでも<b>クラウドAIには及びません</b>。</p><h2>免責事項</h2><p>これは実験的な機能です。回答はAIが生成したもので、不正確な場合があり、<b>金融アドバイスではありません</b>。これらに基づく判断について一切の責任を負いません。</p>]]></string>
</resources>
