<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info_backup_title">备份与恢复</string>
    <string name="info_backup_content"><![CDATA[<h2>本地备份</h2><p><b>备份到文件</b>将您的完整数据库导出为 ZIP 文件，可保存到任意位置。</p><p><b>自动备份</b>在数据发生更改时自动将备份保存到您选择的文件夹。</p><p><b>从文件恢复</b>导入之前导出的 ZIP 文件，这将替换所有当前数据。</p><h2>云端备份</h2><p>云端备份将加密副本存储在您的 Google 云端硬盘中，只有您才能使用密码短语解密。</p><p><b>自动备份</b>在每次更改后自动上传。</p><p><b>立即备份</b>无论自动备份设置如何，均触发立即上传。</p><p><b>密码短语</b>用于加密您的备份，不会存储在设备上。没有密码短语，云端备份将无法恢复。</p><p>最多保留 5 个备份版本，旧版本将自动删除。</p><h2>跨设备同步</h2><p>连接到 Google 云端硬盘后，您可以启用<b>跨设备同步</b>，在登录同一备份的所有设备上持续同步数据。</p><p>在一台设备上所做的更改将同步到其他设备，您可以重命名或从同步列表中移除设备。</p><h2>恢复</h2><p>恢复备份将<b>替换所有当前数据</b>，应用将在成功恢复后重启。</p><p>对于云端恢复，您需要创建备份时使用的密码短语。</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_banksync_title">银行同步</string>
    <string name="info_banksync_content"><![CDATA[<h2>How it works</h2><p>MoneyM imports your bank transactions as <b>suggestions</b> — nothing is added to your books until you accept it. Rejected suggestions are never asked about again, but stay visible under Rejected.</p><h2>Set up Enable Banking</h2><p>Bank access runs through <b>Enable Banking</b>, free for personal use on your own accounts.</p><ul><li>Create an account at <a href="https://enablebanking.com">enablebanking.com</a> and open the Control Panel.</li><li>Register an application in the <b>production</b> environment (sandbox cannot reach real banks) and set its redirect URL to exactly <a href="https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html">https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html</a>.</li><li>Download the application's private key (PEM file). It is shown only once — keep it safe.</li><li>Copy the Application ID shown on the application page.</li><li>Activate the application by <b>linking your own bank account</b>: choose the country, your bank and the account type (personal or business), then sign in at your bank to confirm. Only linked accounts are accessible — that is what keeps personal use free.</li></ul><h2>Connect in the app</h2><p>Paste the Application ID and the key contents into the Bank sync screen and tap <b>Save and validate</b>. Then tap <b>Connect a bank</b>: choose the same country and bank and approve access in the browser. You are sent back to the app automatically; if not, paste the redirect link manually.</p><p>Assign each linked bank account to a wallet so accepted transactions land in the right place.</p><h2>Good to know</h2><p>Bank consent is valid for up to <b>180 days</b>; reconnect when the app asks.</p><p>Automatic sync runs when the app starts, at most every 6 hours. <b>Sync now</b> works anytime.</p><p>Only booked transactions are imported — recent card payments can show up a day or two later, once your bank books them.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_title">AI 分析</string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_content"><![CDATA[<h2>快照与工具</h2><p><b>快照</b>会将所选年份的精简摘要发送给模型——该时段的合计、分类和余额。它速度快，适用于所有引擎，最适合针对该特定年份的问题。</p><p><b>工具</b>让模型可搜索你的全部历史记录，只提取所需的数据。最适合跨越多年的开放式问题。部分较小的模型不支持工具；此时应用会自动回退到快照。</p><h2>设备端处理</h2><p>所有分析<b>完全在你的设备上</b>运行。你的财务数据和问题绝不会离开手机，也不会发送到任何服务器。</p><p>代价是质量。设备端模型远小于云端模型，因此会犯更多错误、遗漏细节，推理也更不可靠。<b>越小的模型表现越差</b>——极小的模型快但弱，更大的设备端模型较慢但更强。即便是最好的设备端模型也<b>不及云端 AI</b>。</p><h2>免责声明</h2><p>这是实验性功能。回答由 AI 生成，可能不准确，<b>并非财务建议</b>。对据此作出的决定不承担任何责任。</p>]]></string>
</resources>
