<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info_backup_title">Biztonsági mentés &amp; Visszaállítás</string>
    <string name="info_backup_content"><![CDATA[<h2>Helyi biztonsági mentés</h2><p><b>Mentés fájlba</b> exportálja a teljes adatbázisát ZIP fájlként, amelyet bárhova menthet.</p><p><b>Automatikus mentés</b> automatikusan elmenti a biztonsági mentést egy Ön által választott mappába, valahányszor az adatok megváltoznak.</p><p><b>Visszaállítás fájlból</b> importál egy korábban exportált ZIP-et. Ez felváltja az összes jelenlegi adatot.</p><h2>Felhőalapú biztonsági mentés</h2><p>A felhőalapú biztonsági mentés egy titkosított másolatot tárol a Google Drive-on. Csak Ön tudja visszafejteni a jelszavával.</p><p><b>Automatikus mentés</b> minden változtatás után automatikusan feltölt.</p><p><b>Mentés most</b> azonnali feltöltést indít az automatikus mentés beállításától függetlenül.</p><p><b>Jelszó</b> titkosítja a biztonsági mentést. Soha nem tárolódik az eszközön. Nélküle a felhőalapú mentés nem állítható vissza.</p><p>Legfeljebb 5 biztonsági mentési verzió kerül megőrzésre; a régebbiek automatikusan törlődnek.</p><h2>Eszközök közötti szinkronizálás</h2><p>A Google Drive-hoz való csatlakozás után engedélyezheti az <b>eszközök közötti szinkronizálást</b>, hogy az összes ugyanahhoz a mentéshez bejelentkezett eszközön folyamatosan szinkronban tartsa adatait.</p><p>Az egyik eszközön végrehajtott változtatások átkerülnek a többire, és az eszközöket átnevezheti vagy eltávolíthatja a szinkronizálási listáról.</p><h2>Visszaállítás</h2><p>A biztonsági mentés visszaállítása <b>felváltja az összes jelenlegi adatot</b>. Az alkalmazás újraindul a sikeres visszaállítás után.</p><p>A felhőből való visszaállításhoz szükség van a mentés létrehozásakor használt jelszóra.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_banksync_title">Banki szinkronizálás</string>
    <string name="info_banksync_content"><![CDATA[<h2>How it works</h2><p>MoneyM imports your bank transactions as <b>suggestions</b> — nothing is added to your books until you accept it. Rejected suggestions are never asked about again, but stay visible under Rejected.</p><h2>Set up Enable Banking</h2><p>Bank access runs through <b>Enable Banking</b>, which provides PSD2/open-banking coverage for supported European banks and countries.</p><ul><li>Create an account at <a href="https://enablebanking.com">enablebanking.com</a> and open the Control Panel.</li><li>Register an application in the <b>production</b> environment (sandbox cannot reach real banks) and set its redirect URL to exactly <a href="https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html">https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html</a>.</li><li>Download the application's private key (PEM file). It is shown only once — keep it safe.</li><li>Copy the Application ID shown on the application page.</li><li>Activate the application by <b>linking a supported bank account</b>: choose the country, your bank and the account type (personal or business), then sign in at your bank to confirm. Availability depends on the bank and country you pick.</li></ul><h2>Connect in the app</h2><p>Paste the Application ID and the key contents into the Bank sync screen and tap <b>Save and validate</b>. Then tap <b>Connect a bank</b>: choose the same country and bank and approve access in the browser. You are sent back to the app automatically; if not, paste the redirect link manually.</p><p>Assign each linked bank account to a wallet so accepted transactions land in the right place.</p><h2>Good to know</h2><p>Bank consent is valid for up to <b>180 days</b>; reconnect when the app asks.</p><p>Automatic sync runs when the app starts, at most every 6 hours. <b>Sync now</b> works anytime.</p><p>Only booked transactions are imported — recent card payments can show up a day or two later, once your bank books them.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_title">MI-elemzés</string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_content"><![CDATA[<h2>Snapshot vs Tools</h2><p><b>Snapshot</b> sends a compact summary of the selected year to the selected AI engine: totals, categories, and balances for that period. It is fast, works on every engine, and is best when your question is about that specific year.</p><p><b>Tools</b> lets supported engines search your full history and pull only the records needed for the answer. It is best for open-ended questions that span more than one year. Some engines or smaller models do not support tools; when that happens the app falls back to a snapshot automatically.</p><h2>AI engines and privacy</h2><p>AI analysis can use on-device engines or external providers, depending on the engine you select. On-device engines run locally, so your financial data and questions stay on your device.</p><p>External providers can be more capable, but the selected snapshot, tool results, and your question are sent to that provider to generate the answer. Use an external provider only if you trust it with the data included in the analysis.</p><p>Quality varies by engine and model. Smaller on-device models are faster but weaker; larger local models and cloud models are usually more capable, but can still make mistakes.</p><h2>Disclaimer</h2><p>This is an experimental feature. Responses are AI-generated, may be inaccurate, and are <b>not financial advice</b>. No responsibility is taken for decisions made based on them.</p>]]></string>
</resources>
