<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info_backup_title">النسخ الاحتياطي &amp; الاستعادة</string>
    <string name="info_backup_content"><![CDATA[<h2>النسخ الاحتياطي المحلي</h2><p><b>النسخ الاحتياطي إلى ملف</b> يصدّر قاعدة بياناتك الكاملة كملف ZIP يمكنك حفظه في أي مكان.</p><p><b>النسخ الاحتياطي التلقائي</b> يحفظ نسخة احتياطية تلقائياً إلى مجلد تختاره في كل مرة تتغير فيها البيانات.</p><p><b>الاستعادة من ملف</b> يستورد ملف ZIP تم تصديره مسبقاً. يؤدي ذلك إلى استبدال جميع البيانات الحالية.</p><h2>النسخ الاحتياطي السحابي</h2><p>يخزّن النسخ الاحتياطي السحابي نسخة مشفرة في Google Drive الخاص بك. أنت وحدك يمكنك فك تشفيرها بعبارة المرور الخاصة بك.</p><p><b>النسخ الاحتياطي التلقائي</b> يرفع النسخة تلقائياً بعد كل تغيير.</p><p><b>نسخ احتياطي الآن</b> يُشغّل رفعاً فورياً بصرف النظر عن إعداد النسخ الاحتياطي التلقائي.</p><p><b>عبارة المرور</b> تُشفّر نسختك الاحتياطية. لا يتم تخزينها على الجهاز أبداً. بدونها، لا يمكن استعادة النسخ الاحتياطي السحابي.</p><p>يتم الاحتفاظ بما يصل إلى 5 إصدارات من النسخ الاحتياطية؛ تُحذف النسخ الأقدم تلقائياً.</p><h2>المزامنة عبر الأجهزة</h2><p>بمجرد الاتصال بـ Google Drive، يمكنك تفعيل <b>المزامنة عبر الأجهزة</b> للحفاظ على تزامن بياناتك باستمرار عبر كل جهاز مسجّل في نفس النسخ الاحتياطية.</p><p>تُسحب التغييرات التي تجريها على جهاز واحد إلى الأجهزة الأخرى، ويمكنك إعادة تسمية الأجهزة أو إزالتها من قائمة المزامنة.</p><h2>الاستعادة</h2><p>استعادة نسخة احتياطية <b>تستبدل جميع البيانات الحالية</b>. سيُعاد تشغيل التطبيق بعد الاستعادة الناجحة.</p><p>للاستعادة من السحابة، تحتاج إلى عبارة المرور المستخدمة عند إنشاء النسخة الاحتياطية.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_banksync_title">مزامنة البنك</string>
    <string name="info_banksync_content"><![CDATA[<h2>How it works</h2><p>MoneyM imports your bank transactions as <b>suggestions</b> — nothing is added to your books until you accept it. Rejected suggestions are never asked about again, but stay visible under Rejected.</p><h2>Set up Enable Banking</h2><p>Bank access runs through <b>Enable Banking</b>, which provides PSD2/open-banking coverage for supported European banks and countries.</p><ul><li>Create an account at <a href="https://enablebanking.com">enablebanking.com</a> and open the Control Panel.</li><li>Register an application in the <b>production</b> environment (sandbox cannot reach real banks) and set its redirect URL to exactly <a href="https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html">https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html</a>.</li><li>Download the application's private key (PEM file). It is shown only once — keep it safe.</li><li>Copy the Application ID shown on the application page.</li><li>Activate the application by <b>linking a supported bank account</b>: choose the country, your bank and the account type (personal or business), then sign in at your bank to confirm. Availability depends on the bank and country you pick.</li></ul><h2>Connect in the app</h2><p>Paste the Application ID and the key contents into the Bank sync screen and tap <b>Save and validate</b>. Then tap <b>Connect a bank</b>: choose the same country and bank and approve access in the browser. You are sent back to the app automatically; if not, paste the redirect link manually.</p><p>Assign each linked bank account to a wallet so accepted transactions land in the right place.</p><h2>Good to know</h2><p>Bank consent is valid for up to <b>180 days</b>; reconnect when the app asks.</p><p>Automatic sync runs when the app starts, at most every 6 hours. <b>Sync now</b> works anytime.</p><p>Only booked transactions are imported — recent card payments can show up a day or two later, once your bank books them.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_title">تحليل الذكاء الاصطناعي</string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_content"><![CDATA[<h2>Snapshot vs Tools</h2><p><b>Snapshot</b> sends a compact summary of the selected year to the selected AI engine: totals, categories, and balances for that period. It is fast, works on every engine, and is best when your question is about that specific year.</p><p><b>Tools</b> lets supported engines search your full history and pull only the records needed for the answer. It is best for open-ended questions that span more than one year. Some engines or smaller models do not support tools; when that happens the app falls back to a snapshot automatically.</p><h2>AI engines and privacy</h2><p>AI analysis can use on-device engines or external providers, depending on the engine you select. On-device engines run locally, so your financial data and questions stay on your device.</p><p>External providers can be more capable, but the selected snapshot, tool results, and your question are sent to that provider to generate the answer. Use an external provider only if you trust it with the data included in the analysis.</p><p>Quality varies by engine and model. Smaller on-device models are faster but weaker; larger local models and cloud models are usually more capable, but can still make mistakes.</p><h2>Disclaimer</h2><p>This is an experimental feature. Responses are AI-generated, may be inaccurate, and are <b>not financial advice</b>. No responsibility is taken for decisions made based on them.</p>]]></string>
</resources>
