<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="info_backup_title">Back-up &amp; Herstel</string>
    <string name="info_backup_content"><![CDATA[<h2>Lokale back-up</h2><p><b>Back-up naar bestand</b> exporteert uw volledige database als een ZIP-bestand dat u overal kunt opslaan.</p><p><b>Automatische back-up</b> slaat automatisch een back-up op in een map naar keuze wanneer gegevens wijzigen.</p><p><b>Herstellen vanuit bestand</b> importeert een eerder geëxporteerde ZIP. Dit vervangt alle huidige gegevens.</p><h2>Cloudback-up</h2><p>Cloudback-up bewaart een versleutelde kopie op uw Google Drive. Alleen u kunt deze ontsleutelen met uw wachtwoordzin.</p><p><b>Automatische back-up</b> uploadt automatisch na elke wijziging.</p><p><b>Nu back-up maken</b> start een onmiddellijke upload ongeacht de instelling voor automatische back-up.</p><p><b>Wachtwoordzin</b> versleutelt uw back-up. Deze wordt nooit op het apparaat opgeslagen. Zonder deze kan de cloudback-up niet worden hersteld.</p><p>Er worden maximaal 5 back-upversies bewaard; oudere worden automatisch verwijderd.</p><h2>Synchronisatie tussen apparaten</h2><p>Zodra verbonden met Google Drive kunt u <b>synchronisatie tussen apparaten</b> inschakelen om uw gegevens continu gesynchroniseerd te houden op elk apparaat dat is aangemeld bij dezelfde back-up.</p><p>Wijzigingen op één apparaat worden naar de andere gepulld, en u kunt apparaten hernoemen of verwijderen uit de synchronisatielijst.</p><h2>Herstellen</h2><p>Een back-up herstellen <b>vervangt alle huidige gegevens</b>. De app herstart na een succesvolle herstelbewerking.</p><p>Voor cloudherstel heeft u de wachtwoordzin nodig die werd gebruikt bij het maken van de back-up.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_banksync_title">Banksynchronisatie</string>
    <string name="info_banksync_content"><![CDATA[<h2>How it works</h2><p>MoneyM imports your bank transactions as <b>suggestions</b> — nothing is added to your books until you accept it. Rejected suggestions are never asked about again, but stay visible under Rejected.</p><h2>Set up Enable Banking</h2><p>Bank access runs through <b>Enable Banking</b>, which provides PSD2/open-banking coverage for supported European banks and countries.</p><ul><li>Create an account at <a href="https://enablebanking.com">enablebanking.com</a> and open the Control Panel.</li><li>Register an application in the <b>production</b> environment (sandbox cannot reach real banks) and set its redirect URL to exactly <a href="https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html">https://davidvster.github.io/moneym.github.io/bank-callback.html</a>.</li><li>Download the application's private key (PEM file). It is shown only once — keep it safe.</li><li>Copy the Application ID shown on the application page.</li><li>Activate the application by <b>linking a supported bank account</b>: choose the country, your bank and the account type (personal or business), then sign in at your bank to confirm. Availability depends on the bank and country you pick.</li></ul><h2>Connect in the app</h2><p>Paste the Application ID and the key contents into the Bank sync screen and tap <b>Save and validate</b>. Then tap <b>Connect a bank</b>: choose the same country and bank and approve access in the browser. You are sent back to the app automatically; if not, paste the redirect link manually.</p><p>Assign each linked bank account to a wallet so accepted transactions land in the right place.</p><h2>Good to know</h2><p>Bank consent is valid for up to <b>180 days</b>; reconnect when the app asks.</p><p>Automatic sync runs when the app starts, at most every 6 hours. <b>Sync now</b> works anytime.</p><p>Only booked transactions are imported — recent card payments can show up a day or two later, once your bank books them.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_title">AI-analyse</string>
    <string name="info_aianalysis_content"><![CDATA[<h2>Snapshot vs Tools</h2><p><b>Snapshot</b> sends a compact summary of the selected year to the selected AI engine: totals, categories, and balances for that period. It is fast, works on every engine, and is best when your question is about that specific year.</p><p><b>Tools</b> lets supported engines search your full history and pull only the records needed for the answer. It is best for open-ended questions that span more than one year. Some engines or smaller models do not support tools; when that happens the app falls back to a snapshot automatically.</p><h2>AI engines and privacy</h2><p>AI analysis can use on-device engines or external providers, depending on the engine you select. On-device engines run locally, so your financial data and questions stay on your device.</p><p>External providers can be more capable, but the selected snapshot, tool results, and your question are sent to that provider to generate the answer. Use an external provider only if you trust it with the data included in the analysis.</p><p>Quality varies by engine and model. Smaller on-device models are faster but weaker; larger local models and cloud models are usually more capable, but can still make mistakes.</p><h2>Disclaimer</h2><p>This is an experimental feature. Responses are AI-generated, may be inaccurate, and are <b>not financial advice</b>. No responsibility is taken for decisions made based on them.</p>]]></string>
</resources>
